CONTACT

ERNEST MATENJWA

alexmatenjwa@gmail.com

0729476167

https://ernestmatenjwa.github.io/ernestmatenjwa.com/



OBJECTIVE

I regard myself as a person who is fascinated by challenges in all sorts of way, work or life, that is merely based on my belief that evolving and adapting to challenges is the whole concept of being competitive and that is what i want to bring to the workplace. With the less experience that i have only means i have more room for improvement especially in programming languages, I have taught myself a few and am willing to learn and be productive as a software developer.

EXPERIENCE

SEP 2022 - Present

Software Developer

Kayise IT

I am working as a fullstack developer, My duties is creating web, mobile and desktop application and creating databases. lauguages we are using are C#, html and css, php, flutter etc

MAY 2021 - MAR 2022

Software Developer

MLAP(codetribe)

I was working as a fullstack developer My duties was to create web and mobile applications using using React.JS, React Native for frontend, AWS(Amplify, S3, dynamodb etc) and firebase for backend

DEC 2020 - MAY2021

Software Developer

ICEP

I was working as a fullstack developer my duties was mostly backend. I was creating APIs and databases using NodeJS and Express Framework. I managed also to familialize myself with Angular for creating HTTP services and user interface

EDUCATION

2021

National diploma in Information & Communication Technology(Software development)

TSHWANE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

2015

National Senior Certificate(Bachelors degree)
Sibusisiwe high school

SKILLS

- C++
- Ambercadero(C++ builder)
- HTML & CSS
- PHP

- · SQL and PL SQL
- React and React Native
- AWS(Amplify, S3, Dynamodb etc)
- Javascript
- Angular
- · Microsoft office
- Flutter
- Git
- · Figma and Framer

INTERESTS

- Surfing through internet
- Programming/ Coding
- Learning

REFERENCE

• Mr K Malatji - "ICEP"

Mentor malatji@icep.co.za +27 123 8295 98

• N Zondo - "MLAP(Codetribe) "

Facilitator nathanael@mlab.co.za +27 60 785 4002

• TM Sibandze - "GWPFI"

Pastor +27 60 2534 68